## **NASIR UDDIN MOJUMDER**

Address: House No-13, Road No-18, Sector No-14, Uttara Dhaka, 1230

Contact: +8801821333196

**E-mail:** Nasir.mamun81@gmail.com, nasir.mamun81@yahoo.com **LinkedIn:**linkedin.com/in/nasir-uddin-mojumder-57238a125/



#### **Career Summary:**

Graduated with MBA degree in Marketing and BBA in Accounting from East West University. Have Fifteen months of professional experience through working as a Business Development Executive at Arteka Bangladesh. Apart from that I also worked as an Intern for three months at Export Import Bank Limited (EXIM Bank Limited). Within this time period, I gained lots of experience about corporate environment. Based on my education and experience, I would like to be a part of an organization to face new challenges and develop strategies to complete all task effectively and efficiently while also disseminating knowledge and gathering experience.

## **Employment History:**

Total Years of Experience: 1.5 years

#### 1. Business Development Executive (November, 2018 – January 2020)

#### Arteka Bangladesh

Address: 09, Badshartak, Jashimuddin Avenue Uttara Dhaka, 1230

### **Responsibilities:**

- Generating leads
- Maintaining relationships with clients and address their needs effectively
- Working with the team to achieve short and long term revenue and profit growth
- Travelling to customer sites and tradeshows to promote company's products and services
- Attending client conferences and meetings in order to network with new and existing contacts
- Procuring new clients through direct contact, word-of-mouth, and collaboration with marketing department
- Negotiating with clients to secure the most attractive prices

### 2. Internship (January, 2018 - April, 2018)

#### **EXIM Bank Bangladesh Ltd**

Branch: Garib-e-Newaz Avenue, Uttara Dhaka Department: General Banking, Investment

### **Duties/Responsibilities:**

- Maintaining registers across different departments
- Organizing the client's CIB files and sharia files
- Auditing defaulter clients Firm
- Giving information about the financing process
- Filling up the application form

## **Academic Qualification:**

## MBA in Marketing (Passing Year June 2021)

East West University, Dhaka Bangladesh CGPA 3.30

#### BBA in Accounting (Minor HRM) 2018

East West University, Dhaka Bangladesh

CGPA: 2.99

#### **HSC in Business Studies 2012**

Adamjee Cantonment College, Dhaka Bangladesh, Dhaka Board

CGPA: 4.80

#### SSC in Business Studies 2010

Chhagalnaiya Academy, Feni Bangladesh, Cumilla Board

CGPA: 4.63

## **Specialization:**

Good Customer Relationship

Negotiation and Decision making skills

## **Extra-Curricular Activities:**

General Member East West University Investment and Finance Club (May 2017- November 2017)

## **Language Proficiency:**

Language	Reading	Writing	Speaking
Bangla	High	High	High
English	High	High	Medium

# **Personal Details:**

Father's Name : Ahasan Ullah Mojumder

Mother's Name : Sufia Akter
Date of Birth : April 2, 1994

Gender : Male

Nationality : Bangladeshi

Permanent Address : Holding# 165, Village: East Darbarpur, PO: Munshirhut, Thana: Fulgazi, District: Feni

Current Location : Dhaka

# Reference(s):

Name : Mr. Abu Sadat Muhammad Ashif Mr. Monjur Hossain
Organization : East West University, Dhaka Arteka Bangladesh

Organization : East West University, Dhaka Arteka Bangladesh
Designation : Assistant Professor, BBA Department Marketing Manager

Mobile : +8801913373155 +8801912450664

E-Mail : ashif@ewubd.edu monjurh664@gmail.com

Relation : Academic Professional